byronkatie.com 2013-10-01

# Privacy statement :: The Work of Byron Katie

  |    
Any information you give to Byron Katie International Inc. and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. 

A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to let us know. 

We do not collect any personal information from users who browse our website. Users browse anonymously. We do analyze our website logs to collect aggregate data—such as the number of hits per page—and use this data to improve the value of the materials available on our website. We also collect information voluntarily given to us by our registered customers on certain protected registration or subscription areas of the site as well as the web store. This data is used for internal purposes only. The **Institute for The Work** has its own set of privacy requirements. If you decide to join the community, you accept responsibility for your profile information. 

Our website logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site. We also track content usage and traffic on the site by using “cookies,” a feature of your browser. There is no personal data collected by the cookies. Instead, these software tags record information such as a user’s browser type and the specific sections that a user visited while on our site. Cookies don't tell us who you are, your email address, or anything personal. You can choose, with your browser, not to accept cookies. If you choose not to accept cookies, you may not be able to view all areas of our website. 

Some areas of our website may be password-protected. In other select areas, which may include free downloads, newsletter, or other offers, we may request that you provide us with basic information before granting you access to the area. If you choose not to register and provide this information, you can still use most of the site. However, you will not be able to access areas that require registration. 

Please note that anything you post on our blog at byronkatie.com is not protected. In addition, this site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

**Privacy of our e-mail lists**  
We maintain several email lists to keep interested parties informed about Byron Katie, her events, products, and more. Individuals must voluntarily request to join our mailing lists by signing up through a form or other means on our website or providing us with their email address at an event, seminar, direct-mail response, or other channel. We do not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease the addresses on our list to anyone. 

You can request to no longer receive email from us. To opt out of our email list, reply to one of our emails and request to be removed or send an email to webmaster@thework.com. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us. 

|   |    
This site and all content in this site may not be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, distributed, or used for the creation of derivative works without prior written consent from Byron Katie International (BKI), except that BKI grants you non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited permission to access and display the web pages within this site, solely on your computer and for your personal, non-commercial use of this website. This permission is conditioned on your not modifying the content displayed on this site; your keeping intact all copyright, trademark, and other proprietary notices; and your acceptance of any terms, conditions, and notices accompanying the content or otherwise set forth in this site. Notwithstanding the foregoing, any content, text, audio, images, and other materials that are made available for downloading, access, or other use from this site with their own license terms, conditions, and notices will be governed by such terms, conditions, and notices. 

THE SCHOOL FOR THE WORK and  
CERTIFICATION PROGRAM

There is only one authorized School for The Work, and it is presented by Byron Katie, who invites you to this powerful opportunity to discover that freedom is possible in every moment. The following sites are authorized websites for The Work: 

  * thework.com 
  * byronkatie.com 
  * instituteforthework.com 
  * livewithbyronkatie.com
  * storeforthework.com

Any other website that presents a school for The Work or a certification program for The Work is illegitimate. There are many people on the Internet today advertising workshops, courses, or trainings in The Work. Please don’t be fooled if you should stumble onto unauthorized certification programs for The Work. Facilitators/trainers who are certified and therefore authorized through Byron Katie International will always have a Certified Facilitator for The Work logo on their website, assuring you that what they offer is legitimate. For your convenience and for official verification, we proudly list these websites and profiles and their contact information on thework.com/facilitators.php
